Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional Material, 1938-2011, bulk 1954-2011; 1954-2011; Series 3; 187 Linear Feet
  - 4th of July - Kids 1, July 2, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 4)
  - 4th of July - Kids 2, July 2, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 5)
  - "60 Minutes" & "Hire Rosa Martinez", September 27, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 9)
  - 60 Radio Spots, undated; Series 3; audio casette tape (Box 4031, Folder 3)
  - 60-Second Film - "Teaching Career Month (April), For use ending April 30, 1963, Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 19)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "American Education Week (November 10-16), For use through November 16", 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 2)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "American Education Week (November 10 thru 16), For use through November 16, 1963", Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 20)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "American Education Week (April 1 thru 30), For use through April 30, 1964", Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 21)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "American Education Week (November 17 thru 13), For use thru November 13, 1965", Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 22)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "American Education Week (November 5-12), For use through November 12, 1966", Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 23)
  - 60-Second TV Spot - "Teaching Career Month (April), For use ending April 30, 1963, Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 23)
  - 60-Second Television Spot - "Teaching Career Month (April 1 thru 30), For use thru April 30, 1964", Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 3)
  - 60-Sec. TV Spot - "American Education Week 1964 (November 8-14), For use through november 14', Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 25)
  - A Chance to Serve Film Strip - 7 1/2 IPS Taped NARRATION - Guide Scrip[t], Undated; Series 3; Filmstrip - 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3671, Folder 2)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 File 2 Filmstrip
  - A Chance to Serve Film Strip - 7 1/2 IPS Taped NARRATION - Guide Scrip[t], Undated; Series 3; Filmstrip - 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3671, Folder 3)
    Separated material found in Box 3670 File 3
  - A Million or More by '64, Undated; Series 3; Pre-recorded program 7:5 I.P.S. Magnetic Sound Recording Tape (Box 3674, Folder 2)
    Separated materials found in Box 3673 File 8 Filmstrip
  - A Plan For Your Future - produced by NEA Special Services Color Filmstrip, 1967; Series 3; 33 1/3 rpm Long Playing Time: approx. 13 mins. Audible signal for manual equipment - Use other side for automatic projection with 30/50 cycle inaudible signal (Box 3672, Folder 5)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 File 7 2 Filmstrips
  - ABC Channel 7 11:30pm "Nightline" Dole Resigns, May 15, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3952, Folder 2)
  - "Achievement Gaps Grants Project", a video report on Hamilton Co., TN; Milwaukee & Seattle, Undated; Series 3; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 23)
  - Achieving Professional Governance - Minnesota/Pennsylvania, 1972; Series 3; 2 Audio cassettes (Box 3671, Folder 6)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 File 6 2 Filmstrips
  - Aim for Excellence- Guide and Script, February 1962; Series 3; Aim for Excellence - Narrated by Douglas Edwards - Produced by NEA - Gotham Recording Corporation 33 1/3 rpm Long Playing 9 min 46 sec. Inaudible Signal (Box 3672, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in 3656 File 4 2 Filmstrips
  - Alabama Education Association "Celebrating a Successful Merger", August 1, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 3)
  - Alaska #1, January 27, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape, audio channel 2 only (Box 3952, Folder 3)
  - Alaska #2, January 27, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape, audio channel 2 only (Box 3952, Folder 4)
  - Alaska's Children Deserve the Best, March 21, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3952, Folder 5)
  - Albanian Elections 1992, March 12, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 10)
  - Al Gore / Letterman, September 8, 1993; Series 3 (Box 3960, Folder 2)
  - All in a Lifetime, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3971, Folder 11)
  - American Education Reform with Keith Geiger, August 8, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 10)
  - American Education Week, undated; Series 3 (Box 3994, Folder 35)
    American Education Week
  - American Education Week, undated; series 3 (Box 4551, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week (1964), Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week 60-Second Spot (1964) B-106, Series 3 (Box 3972, Folder 8)
  - American Education Week B-126 [1/2], undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3971, Folder 12)
  - American Education Week B-126 [2/2], undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week Spot (1957), Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week Spot Gosec, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 9)
  - American Education Week Spots, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week TV Spots (1962), Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 10)
  - And Gladly Teach, 1953; series 3 (Box 4531, Folder 1)
  - And Gladly Teach, 1953; series 3 (Box 4530, Folder 1)
  - "And No Bells Ring" Rental Print, undated; Series 3 (Box 4059, Folder 1)
  - ...And Something More, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3971, Folder 13)
  - Ann Davis - Illinois Interview, January 9, 2008; Series 3; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 58)
  - Answers and Questions, 1968; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 12)
  - Apple Computer "Project 2000", February 23, 1988; Series 3; BETACAM video tape, audio both channels mixed (Box 3952, Folder 7)
  - Approaches to Teaching Values Education - Filmstrip, Cassette tape, Script - A Naional Education Association Publication - Stock No. 0-8106-1123-6-00, 1976; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 3671, Folder 5)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 File 5 Filmstrip
  - Approaches To Teaching Values, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_da87469be3260c6f66cfa44b4d76c282)
  - Are out Schools Up to Date?, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 13)
  - Assessment Tape 1, Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 5)
  - Arlington Cemetary - Kennedy Gravesites, May 15, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 6)
  - Art Hungerford - SDC KINE, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 31)
  - Art Hungerford - SDC Kine, undated; series 3 (Box 4580, Folder 1)
  - Asian/Pacific Islander Observance, May 1, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3977, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta, GA Scenes - "The Underground at Night", April 17, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 7)
  - Auditions for Substitute Representative for CBS-TV "The Great Adventure" POMROY - NORMAN - MURPHY - WATSON, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 1)
  - "A Very Special Dance" Color - Length 15:00, Undated; Series 3; 16 mm (Box 3554, Folder 1)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3649, 3654, 3655, 3651, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - "A Very Special Dance" Color - Length 15:00, Undated; Series 3; 16 mm (Box 3554, Folder 3)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3654, 3655, 3648, 3651, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - A Very Special Dance - NEA-Audio - Visual, Undated; Series 3; 16 mm (Box 3650, Folder 1)
  - Awards Dinner, June 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape no audio (Box 3952, Folder 8)
  - Awards Dinner 2, June 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 11)
  - Back-to-School Spot with Dr. Jonas salk, Van Cilburn, Mickey Mantle, Sept. 1958; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 13)
  - A Band is..., 1973; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 2)
  - Barney Frank - "I Have a Dream", June 16, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 4)
  - Baseball Action 1. Music & Effects, 2. Music Only, 3. Effects Only, 4. Effects Only, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3952, Folder 9)
  - Baseball Spots (26) - "Joey and Chris", undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3977, Folder 6)
  - Baseball Spots (26) - "Working Out", undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3977, Folder 7)
  - Beber Silverstein & Partners, July 17, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 8)
  - The Big Classroom, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 3)
  - Bike Ride for Education, July 3, 1996; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3997, Folder 9)
  - Bill Clinton/NEA: Together for Education, April 6, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape audio mixed both channels (Box 3952, Folder 10)
  - Bill Clinton Town Meeting 1, July 8, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3960, Folder 7)
  - Bill Clinton Town Meeting 2, July 8, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 1)
  - Bob Chanin - Interview for Book, July 15, 2008; Series 3; Chanin, Robert H.; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 57)
  - Bob Chase Message to Idaho Educ. Assoc. for Stakeholder Meeting, January 16, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 5)
  - Bob Chase - National Press Club #1, February 5, 1997; Series 3 (Box 3961, Folder 1)
  - Bob Chase - National Press Club #2, February 5, 1997; Series 3 (Box 3961, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase - National Press Club #1, February 25, 1997; Series 3
  - Bob Chase - National Press Club #2, February 25, 1997; Series 3 (Box 3961, Folder 4)
  - Bob Chase - National Press Club (1998), February 11, 1998; Series 3 (Box 3977, Folder 8)
  - Bob Chase - NEA Auditorium, September 9, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 1)
  - Bob Chase Radio Spot "Inspiring Times" 1, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 1)
  - Bob Chase Radio Spot "Inspiring Times" 2, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase Radio Spot "Inspiring Times", undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 3)
  - Bob Chase Video Message to Becky Fleischauer, Spring 2002; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3997, Folder 10)
  - Bob Chase Video Message to Lee Ann (WEA), May 2, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 6)
  - Bob Dole - Education Speech, Minneapoils, Minn., July 17, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 1)
  - Boston City Scenes Beauty Shots, July 16, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 2)
  - Braulio Alonso Interview, Tampa Florida, with Al-Tony Gilmore, Feburary 7, 2008; Series 3; Alonso, Braulio; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 55)
  - Breakfast with the Champions - Open, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3978, Folder 9)
  - Breakthrough in Education, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 4)
  - The Bright Yellow Schoolbus, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 5)
  - Broadcast Awards, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3961, Folder 5)
  - Broadcast Awards, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3961, Folder 7)
  - Broadcast Awards, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tapes (Box 3961, Folder 8)
  - Broadcast Awards 1992, June 18, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 12)
  - Broadcast Awards 1995, June 22, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 7)
  - Broadcast Awards 1996, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3978, Folder 10)
  - Broadcast Awards '94, June 16, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 4)
  - Broadcast Awards '97, June 20, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 1)
  - Broadcast Awards Title Graphic, June 23, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 2)
  - Broadcast Services "Esprit, #1, vol 1", March 5, 1991; Series 3 (Box 3961, Folder 6)
  - Broadcast SVC (Open & Close w/ Slate), Maty 12, 1987; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 13)
  - Buffy Saint Marie - Of My People You are Dying 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 6)
  - Buffy Saint Marie - Of My People You are Dying 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 7)
  - Building Exterior, NEA HQ, undated; Series 3 (Box 3972, Folder 14)
  - Butch's Retirement (Larry Diebold), December 8, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 3)
  - Cable for the Voiceless (Tony Brown), undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 16)
  - Caddo Parish, Louisiana 1950, Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 8)
  - Can America Afford Better Schools?", 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4202, Folder 1)
  - Carlos Santana - Teachers (National) 1, February 17, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 8)
  - Carlos Santana - Teachers (National) 2, February 17, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 9)
  - Carlos Santana - Teachers (National) 3, February 17, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3998, Folder 10)
  - Cascom International, Inc. "Effect SE1391 Business World" Vol. 7, June 12, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 1)
  - CBC - "NEA & AFT: Working Together for Better Health Plans", November 15, 1986; SSeries 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 2)
  - CBS - NEA Announcements, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 36)
  - CBS - NEA Announcements, undated; series 3 (Box 4508, Folder 1)
  - CCT NEA-Govt. RElations, February 5, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 14)
  - Census B Roll #1, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 2)
  - Census B Roll #2, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 3)
  - Center for the Advancement of Public Education - "Advancing the Public in Public Education", April 14, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 3)
  - Center for National Policy / Gore Tribute, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3961, Folder 10)
  - Century Plaza Bill Clinton "B-Roll" Tape 1, April 8, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 1)
  - Century Plaza Bill Clinton "B-Roll" Tape 2, April 8, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 2)
  - Century Plaza President Clinton Tape 1 "Main Camera", April 8, 1995; Series 3 (Box 3964, Folder 2)
  - Century Plaza President Clinton Tape 2 "Main Camera", April 8, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3964, Folder 3)
    Attached note says "Guns have no place in our schools & have no place in the hands of our children. If we don't start this [zero tolerance] we won't have safe schools"
  - The Challenge, undated; series 3 (Box 4546, Folder 1)
  - The Challenge of Change, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 10)
  - A Chance to Learn 1, 1965; Series 3 (Box 3973, Film 11)
  - A Chance to Learn 2, 1965; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 12)
  - Charter Schools Part 1, March 23-24, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 3)
  - Chevrolet/GEO "Who Are We" Music Video, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 2)
  - Children Without, 1965; series 3 (Box 4533, Folder 1)
  - Children Without, 1965; series 3; 16mm film (Box 4541, Folder 3)
  - Childrens Day Forum, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3964, Folder 4)
  - Choose Children - 12 spots, October 25, 1995; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 20)
  - Choose Children - Many Spots, September 8, 1995; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 21)
  - Christa PSA, March 11, 1986; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 15)
  - Chuck Williams Interview, NEA Minorty Presidents, June 5, 2008; Series 3; Williams, Chuck; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 70)
  - Class of '98 Presentation (New Orleans), June 12, 1998; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 4)
  - Clinton Downlink from L.A., May 14, 1992; Series 3 (Box 3964, Folder 5)
  - Clinton "Kick Butts" Speech 1. Student Intro, 2. Clinton's Speech, 3. Clinton in Crowd, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3962, Folder 6)
  - Clinton in Woodbridge: Pre-speech Activities, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 5)
  - Clinton Interview "A" Camera, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 3)
  - Clinton Interview "B" Camera, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 4)
  - Clinton Intro, July 2, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 3)
  - Clinton News Conference Budget Battle, November 16, 1995; Series 3 (Box 3964, Folder 6)
  - Clinton/Town Meeting, June 20, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3962, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for America's Children "Kissing Babies is Not Enough", March 16, 1992; Series 3 (Box 3962, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining Celebration - 1997 NEA RA - Atlanta, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 4)
  - The Coming Breakthrough in Education, undated; series 3 (Box 4522, Folder 1)
  - Comment and Perspective: Should Teacher's Organize?, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4059, Folder 2)
  - Commitment, October 29, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 4)
  - Commitment to Action, 1967; Series 3; Includes 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS, 25 min; 1 filmstrip; manual and other paper materials. (Box 3668, Folder 5)
    Contains separated material found in box 3676, file 7: filmstrip.
  - Communications/Media Relations "The Interview", March 15, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 5)
  - Community Growth: Crisis and Challenge, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 13)
  - The Continuum of Teacher Development in Action, September 25, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 5)
  - Conversations, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 5)
  - "Cornerstone for the Future" with Keith Geiger Intro, March 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 3)
  - Cornerstone for the Future: Girls and Young Women, 1995; Series 3 (Box 4636, Folder 2)
  - "Cornerstone for the Future: Girls & Young Women" (with Keith Geiger Intro) 1, March 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 4)
  - "Cornerstone for the Future: Girls and Young Women" with K. Gieger Intro 2, March 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 1)
  - Cornerstone of Tomorrow, 1965; series 3 (Box 4535, Folder 4)
  - Cost of Knowledge, 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 14)
  - Craig Phillips, Former NC School Superintendent, Interview on Libby Koontz, March 6, 2008; Series 3; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 66)
  - Crowded Out, 1958; series 3 (Box 4527, Folder 1)
  - Crowded Out, 1958; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 15)
  - "The Curriculum" (Stock # 382-11746) NEA - CSI, Undated; Series 3; 7" Reel 3 3/4 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 9)
  - David Brinkley's Journal, 1962; series 3 (Box 4526, Folder 1)
  - David Henry Hwang, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 2)
  - Debut '91 Sports, June 24, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 5)
  - DCACT-Crabtree Auditorium NEA Hugh Scott Questions + Answers, October 31; Series (Box 4832, Folder 13)
  - Declaration of Independence, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 6)
  - Dennis the Menace Movie Trailer (American Education Week), November 6-12, 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 15)
  - A Desk for Billie, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4059, Folder 3)
  - Detroit Education Association, 1964; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3974, Folder 1)
  - Discipline, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 16)
  - Discipline and Motivation: A Genuine Partnership, R.J. Wlodkowski, 1978; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 16)
  - Don Cameron - "ESP Day", November 4, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 3)
  - Don Cameron Interview by Al-Tony Gilmore, September 28, 2010; Series 3; Cameron, Don; Three audio cassette tapes and manuscript notes from the interview. (Box 3851, Folder 3)
  - "The Don" for Arlene Pavey, May 27, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Carr - Telenews Forecast, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 37)
  - Dr. Carr - Telenews Forecast, undated; series 3 (Box 4509, Folder 1)
  - The Dropout, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3974, Folder 2)
  - Drop Out, March 27, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 16)
  - Dropout 3 Spots, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 7)
  - Drop Out w/ Lionel Cartwright (WVEA Tag), March 12, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 17)
  - "Drug Abuse" 1971 Color - Length: 13:00, Series 3; 16 mm (Box 3554, Folder 1)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3649, 3654, 3655, 3648, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - Duck and Cover, 1952; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 38)
  - Duck and Cover, 1952; series 3 (Box 4510, Folder 1)
  - E. B. Palmer Interview Re: James Harris & Libby Koontz, undated; Series 3 (Box 3682, Folder 65)
  - Ed Asner Radio Spots 1016/1023/1033/1046/1053/1063, July 1981; Series 3; Magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3687, Folder 1)
  - Eddy Narration - Pima Co. Amphitheater, Long Beach, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 4)
  - Edited Version of October 11, 1977 IPD Staff Meeting, Series 3; Reel-to-Reel Video Tape (Box 4707, Folder 7)
  - Education Advocates 2-2, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 6)
  - Education Finance Advocacy Program: Assuring Adequate and Equitable Funding for Public Education, Undated; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 7)
  - Education International Video for Congress, 2001; Series 3 (Box 4636, Folder 3)
  - Electing the President (Reagan), undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 8)
  - Emma Belle Sweet 1, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3974, Folder 3)
  - Emma Belle Sweet 2, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3559, Folder 3)
  - Emerging Educational Opportunites for All: Master with Music and Beeps Ready for Transfer to 3-3/4 Maching Master, 1965; Series 3; 15 IPS magnetic tape master for filmstrip audio track. Filmstrip is not present. (Box 3680, Folder 6)
  - Emerging Educational Opportunites for All: Original Edited Narration with Carr - Less Any Music, 1965; Series 3; 15 IPS magnetic tape master for filmstrip audio track. Filmstrip is not present. (Box 3680, Folder 7)
  - ESP-Explorer 1, May 15, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 4)
  - ESP-Explorer 2, May 15, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 5)
  - ESP-Explorer 3, May 15, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 6)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#1, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5248 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4034, Folder 1)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#2, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5248 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4034, Folder 2)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#3, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4034, Folder 3)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#4, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4034, Folder 4)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#5, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4034, Folder 5)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#6, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4035, Folder 1)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#7, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4035, Folder 2)
  - ESP - PSA - Always There CR#8, October 21, 2002; Series 3; 35mm 5279 ECN Original (35mm magnetic video reel) (Box 4035, Folder 3)
  - An Equal Chance Through Title IX, undated; series 3 (Box 4545, Folder 1)
  - E'Sprit - Volume 1 #1, December 23, 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 5)
  - E'Sprit - Volume 1 #2, April 19, 1990; Series 3 (Box 3999, Folder 6)
  - ESProgress #1, Volume 1, March 5, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 8)
  - ESProgress #1, Volume 2, April 17, 1990; Series 3 (Box 3963, Folder 9)
  - Evelyn Temple's Video Message to Ernie Terrian, June 18, 1998; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 6)